<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<cat xmlns="urn:apple:names:siri:cat:1.0" id="PlayMediaIntent#ConfirmInterruptingAnotherSE" locale="en">
    <conditions>
        <condition name="deviceLocationPresent">
            <expression name="deviceLocation" op="nonempty"/>
        </condition>
        <condition name="roomLocationPresent">
            <expression name="roomLocation" op="nonempty"/>
        </condition>
        <condition name="repromptAndMultipleDevices">
            <and>
                <expression name="reprompt"/>
                <expression name="multipleDevices"/>
            </and>
        </condition>
        <condition name="repromptAndMultipleRooms">
            <and>
                <expression name="reprompt"/>
                <expression name="multipleRooms"/>
            </and>
        </condition>
    </conditions>
    <first>
        <first condition="deviceLocationPresent">
            <first condition="repromptAndMultipleDevices">
                <random>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I didn't quite get that. Do you want to stop audio on other devices to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I missed what you said. Do you want to stop audio on other devices to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I missed that. Do you want to stop audio on other devices to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Hmm, let’s try that again. Do you want to stop audio on other devices to play this?</dialog>
                </random>
            </first>
            <first condition="reprompt">
                <random>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I didn't quite get that. Do you want to stop audio on <var name="deviceLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I missed what you said. Do you want to stop audio on <var name="deviceLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I missed that. Do you want to stop audio on <var name="deviceLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Hmm, let’s try that again. Do you want to stop audio on <var name="deviceLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
                </random>
            </first>
            <dialog condition="multipleDevices">Do you want to stop audio on other devices to play this?</dialog>
            <dialog>Do you want to stop audio on <var name="deviceLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
        </first>
        <first condition="roomLocationPresent">
            <first condition="repromptAndMultipleRooms">
                <random>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I didn't quite get that. Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> and other rooms to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I missed what you said. Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> and other rooms to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I missed that. Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> and other rooms to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Hmm, let’s try that again. Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> and other rooms to play this?</dialog>
                </random>
            </first>
            <first condition="reprompt">
                <random>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I didn't quite get that. Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I missed what you said. Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Sorry, I missed that. Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
                    <dialog>Hmm, let’s try that again. Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
                </random>
            </first>
            <dialog condition="multipleRooms">Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> and other rooms to play this?</dialog>
            <dialog>Do you want to stop audio in <var name="roomLocation"/> to play this?</dialog>
        </first>
        <dialog>Do you want to stop audio elsewhere to play this?</dialog>
    </first>
</cat>
